Kirito, he finally woke up!
Kirito, you're back.
About damn time you snapped out of it.
I knew if I waited around long
enough you wouldn't disappoint me.
We didn't get to finish
things back in Aincrad.
Now, I can check that off my list.
It's showtime, baby.
I don't know.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Is that all you've got?
I want to fight, so get
the lead out already!
Come on, man!
I've been waiting damn
near two years for this!
You'd kill me faster if you dropped that
broken-ass sword and used both hands.
Then you could go after all these others
that were killing your
friends a minute ago.
They only did that
because you made them two.
That's how you do things,
turning people against each other
and watching all hell break loose.
That's what you did with us in SAO.
Oh, that ain't gonna happen here.
Never again.
I'll make sure of that.
Oh, it'll happen again.
Once those players thaw out,
they'll go right back to
slaughtering all of your friends.
Unless your pals kill them first.
There's no honor in killing the
Helpless, but that's the point.
So give the order.
Kill all the red players!
Hey, if you want to be
stubborn, that's cool with me.
I'll kill you either way.
But after I get done with you,
I'm gonna put Lightning Flash,
your whole crew, and every single
Underworld are into coffins.
You can count on that!
Kirito!
Eugeo, please help him.
What the hell?
Let's go. You and me. Chiyo.
Release recollection!
Now what?
It's the life resources
of the foreign players.
Kirito logged them out without making
them suffer the pain of getting killed.
You're going to pay for that, you bastard!
Oh no! Stop him!
Don't worry.
Look it!
Damn it!
What's going on?
Why aren't they coming to me?
Lives are like vessels.
They carry our hopes and
dreams and reflect our souls.
Do you think all these players
from different countries
came here just so they could
be used to kill each other?
Nah, they want to have fun
and explore a cool new world.
A place that's totally different
from anything they know.
A place like the land of
fairies where you and I met.
They want the same as us.
You're right, Yuki.
Release. Recollection.
Son of a bitch!
Eugeo once told me that in the
northernmost part of the human empire,
There was an enormous black cedar tree
and Kirito sword was forged from it.
I see that explains why
it can absorb sacred power
Man, Kirito, you really are the best.
No one from back in
the Aincrad days to now
ever brought out the killer
in me as much as you.
Sex like hell, it's gotta
end after all that time,
but there's no better place
to end it than right here.
Let's you and me have
some fun, Black Swordsman.
Okay, I'm ready when you are.
First element!
Oh, my God.
No!
Now that's what I'm talking about.
But you didn't get rid of me.
Oh, no.
You just logged me out is all.
I'm still gonna keep
coming after you guys.
And I won't stop till I
slit you and Lightning
Flash's throats and
ripped out your hearts.
You can both count on that. Uh-uh.
You're done for good.
You'll never log out of here again.
Count on that.
My sword's made from the Giga Cedar.
A huge tree in Rulid they
couldn't cut down for 200 years.
Till two kids finally did.
I just sent the memory of it into you.
When your friends see all those players
logging out, they'll speed up time,
trapping you in your STL.
It'll be years before you're
let out, if you're lucky.
Then again, folks might want
to build a village here.
They'll need wood and who knows, maybe
a couple kids will chop you down too.
System call, transfer
durability, right to area.
Kitty-toe, you did it again, man.
You saved everyone here, but you've
got to stop hogging all the glory,
dude, because it's getting old.
That cat's off the hook, for real.
He did it!
Thank God he did it! He did!
And I'm so happy!
Ever since I first laid eyes on him,
I had faith in him, that at the last moment,
he and those swords would save us all.
Thank you, everyone.
I won't let your faith in me, or all the
blood and tears you shed, be for nothing.
I mean it. Thank you.
Kirito, Emperor Vecta,
he's after... I know.
It's fuzzy, but I know he's after Alice.
Let's go get her back.
You and me, Asuna.
Come on.
Wait, Kitty-Do, what are you doing?
Hold on tight.
Damn it!
What's that idiot standing around for?
We got a little under 8 hours and 20
minutes to go before the JSDF boards us.
Boss wanted me to crank up the
time again at the 8 hour mark,
but since the other players got wiped out,
might as well do it now.
Whatever you're up to in there,
Vassago, you better hang on.
What?
That figures. I need a key.
We're good at picking locks.
Higa! Hey! Can you hear
me? Come on! Wake up!
How's Kirito?
He's out of danger.
His Fluctlight activity's
been fully restored.
It's a little too active, to be honest.
Really?
Oh, that's good to hear.
I swear, Higa.
You had me scared for a second there.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault that mole got on board.
I should have vetted the staff better.
It's okay, Geeks.
What about Alice in the Underworld?
They're both safe for now.
All the players from the US, China,
and South Korea have logged out.
Wait.
China and South Korea?
They had people logged in from there, too?
Yeah, tons of them.
They posted all over social media,
using their competitiveness as gamers
to rile them up and lure them in.
Uh-huh.
That would do it.
The 2,000 from Japan you
logged in put up a good fight,
but they were mostly wiped out.
At that point, there were still over 20,000
Chinese and South Korean players left.
Luckily, that's when Kirito
woke up, and just like that...
Oh, my God.
That's not good.
Flutlight Acceleration Rate
Safety Limiter disengaged.
15 minutes until maximum
acceleration phase.
For personnel in the STLs, initiate
disengagement protocol immediately. Crap!
Maximum acceleration phase?
Isn't the FLA rate limited
to 1,200 times normal speed?
Only for folks diving.
1,200's the limit for the lifespan
of a real-world human soul.
But for observing, we can't speed
it up more than 5,000 times normal.
That said, the hardware
can go even faster.
But how fast?
The hardware does have
a limit, doesn't it?
During the maximum acceleration phase, the
FLA rate will be just over five million.
The two STLs in Roppongi can't keep up at
that speed, because they're on a sad link.
They'll be disconnected automatically.
But Kirito's and Asuna's
STLs are hardwired.
They're in danger! Come on!
We have to get them out of those
STLs right now, but— No, we can't!
The initial acceleration
phase already started.
If we pull them out of those machines
now, it'll damage their Fluct Lights!
What about the disengagement protocol?
Can we start that?
Hey, Keeks.
I'm going back to the
maintenance connector.
Understood.
But I'm going to go with you.
I think I should be strong enough to
carry you down that ladder on my back.
It's too risky.
Please, sir, let me take him. No.
I need you and the other
agents to defend the stairs.
We have to open the bulkhead again,
which means you'll have to
engage the enemy directly.
Which means the risk is greater for you.
I'm sorry, but that's
the way it has to be.
Sir. Yes, sir.
Wait a sec!
When I was operating the STLs before,
I set us up with an open
channel to talk to Kirito.
He's on line C12.
Hurry up and call him now!
What do I tell him?
Tell him to log himself out!
Is Alice safe? Can you tell?
She hasn't been caught yet, but
there's a massive presence chasing her.
Oh boy.
I hope we can catch up to
her before it's too late.
Kirito, can you hear me?
Kirito, come in! Kikuoka?
How am I hearing you?
I'm not at a console.
Never mind that, just listen.
You're in a lot of danger.
The time acceleration rate is increasing
because the hijackers
disengaged the FLA limiter.
The limiter?
Higa says if you're still in there
when we reach maximum acceleration,
by the time we disconnect you here,
200 years will have passed there. What?
You and Asuna have ten minutes to
reach the console and log out manually.
Depleting your HP is another
option, but it's too risky.
If you die after we reach
maximum acceleration,
you'll spend 200 years in the Underworld
in a state of total sensory deprivation.
Got it.
Me and Asuna are headed for the
console at the World's End Altar.
I'll catch up to Alice
in a bit, so get ready.
We're bringing her, too.
Thanks, but you two are more important.
I want you to prioritize your
escape over securing Alice.
Two hundred years is longer than
the lifespan of a human soul.
So even though we can delete your
memories after logging you out,
if you've been in there that long,
the odds of you regaining consciousness
here would be almost zero.
Don't worry, we'll make it.
We'll all make it.
Oh, and one more thing.
I'm sorry, you know, for
calling you a son of a bitch.
Not at all.
I deserved it, and you can
punch me when you get back.
It looks like he gets ready.
I have to go. Good luck.
You too.
We'll get to that console.
See you in ten.
What did he say?
You sounded like it was serious. Is it?
Well, is it? Not really.
The time here's gonna
speed up in ten minutes.
He wants us to log out before it does.
All right, then.
I wish we could float here
forever, but Alice does need us.
Come on, let's go get her. Hang on.
We'll be going fast.
Amayori and Takiguri, this
is my final order to you.
Return to the human empire
and your nests in the west.
Amayori, find a husband,
and Takiguri, find a wife.
Have many babies and
raise them to be strong.
Strong and brave so that one day they may
carry knights as gallantly
as their parents.
Go home! Go on!
Ama... Yori?
No! Leave it!
Excuse me.
No!
Help me!
What? What?
Ah! Ah!
Kirito...
Oh, oh...
I've been a long time...
How many dreams I've created?
Thank you.
I don't want to cry,
it's better than I am.
I don't want to cry, I
don't want to go away.
I don't want to change anything.
I don't want to keep my heart.
I'm going to connect with you.